{
    "subject": "resource/The_Pleasure_of_His_Company",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Lilli_Palmer",
    "human_readable": "The Pleasure of His Company stars Lilli Palmer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7643181085586548,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie 'The Pleasure of His Company'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7278751134872437,
            "question": "Was Lilli Palmer a popular actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6618250608444214,
            "question": "What is the name of the actress who starred in 'The Pleasure of His Company'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5877369046211243,
            "question": "Are there any other famous actors who appeared in 'The Pleasure of His Company'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5605235695838928,
            "question": "What other roles has Lilli Palmer played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5320597290992737,
            "question": "What movie features Lilli Palmer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4982903301715851,
            "question": "Is Lilli Palmer known for acting in movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45416080951690674,
            "question": "Can you name a film featuring Lilli Palmer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4398997128009796,
            "question": "What year was 'The Pleasure of His Company' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36464571952819824,
            "question": "In what genre of films did Lilli Palmer often appear?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Pleasure of His Company stars Lilli Palmer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3930_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'The Pleasure of His Company' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3930_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a film featuring Lilli Palmer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3930_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Lilli Palmer known for acting in movies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3930_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3930_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3930_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3930_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3930_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3930_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3930_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3930_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3930_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3930_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3930_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Lilli Palmer starred with Fred Astaire and Debbie Reynolds in the 1961 film \"The Pleasure of His Company,\" which confirms the triple \"The Pleasure of His Company stars Lilli Palmer.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}